썰매에 올라 휘파람을 불자
He sprang to his sleigh
To his team gave a whistle
썰매가 날아 올랐습니다
And away they all flew
Like the down of a thistle
그리고 사라지는 뒷모습 따라
이런 소리가 들렸습니다
But I heard him exclaim
Ere he drove out of sight
메리 크리스마스!
모두 안녕히!
"Merry Christmas to all
And to all a good night."
우와! 굉장하다!
정말 네가 쓴거야?
Wow! That was great!
You really wrote that?
요정들아, 잘있거라
난 털사로 간다
Say goodbye, elves.
I'm off to Tulsa.
크리스마스에
떨어져 있어야 하다니!
I can't believe you won't be here
for Christmas.
정말 안올거야?
You're really not coming back?
연말까지 정리해야할 서류가
산더미야
We have this paperwork that needs
to be filed by the end of the year.
그 바보같은 털사 직원들이
맡아서 하면 안돼?
Why can't those dumb Tulsa people
do the work?
왜냐면 그 바보같은
털사 직원들은
Because those dumb people
got everything dumped on them..
뉴욕본사의 거만한 간부들의
일을 떠맡게 됐으니깐
by the arrogant jerks
in the New York office.
난 두세상 사이에 낀 셈이야
I'm caught between two worlds.
- 다 못하면 나 잘려
- 이런법이 어딨어!
- If I don't get it done, I'll be fired.
- It's so unfair.
- 좋아하는 일도 아닌데
- 누군 자기 일 좋아하나?
- You don't even like your job.
- So. Who does?
- 난 내 일 좋아
- 나두
- I like my job.
- I love my job.
- 나도 빨리 출근하고 싶어!
- 공룡들이 너무 그리워!
- I can't wait to go back to work.
- I can't get enough dinosaurs.
미안하지만 난 못와
I'm sorry I won't be here.
평일에 못보는 것도 서러운데
It's hard enough not seeing you
during the week..
크리스마스에도 못보다니!
but for Christmas..
일을 해야한다면
어쩌겠어, 이해해
If this is what you have to do,
I understand.
고마워
Thanks.
새해 첫날보자
I'll see you New Year's Day.
12월 31일도 못와?
You're not gonna be here
New Year's Eve?
- 말 안했던가?
- 안했어
- Did I not mention that?
- No.
그럼 다들 잘있어!
And to all a good night!
프렌즈 시즌 9
'털사의 크리스마스'
여러분
크리스마스 이브에 가족과 함께
All right, everybody.
I know it is Christmas Eve..
보내야 하는건 나도 잘 압니다
and you'd rather be with family,
but there is no call for writing..
그렇다고 "재수없어, 미스터 빙!"
이라고 의자뒤에 붙일건 없잖아요?
"Screw you, Mr. Bing"
on the back of my chair.
그리고 그냥 챈들러라고 불러요
By the way,
you can all call me Chandler.
- 안녕
- 어디 갔다와요?
- Hey.
- Hey. Where you been?
3층 보험회사가 크리스마스
파티한다길래 보고 왔어요
I was checking out that insurance
company's Christmas party on three.
너무 예쁘더라구요!
커다란 트리에 장식까지!
It was really beautiful. They have
decorations and this huge tree.
지옥에나 가라죠!
우린 일해야 하잖아요!
And I just thought,
to hell with them, we have to work.
아무튼 그래서 햄을 훔쳐왔어요
So I stole their ham.
잘됐네요
가족과 함께 있을순 없지만
Hear that?
You may not be with your families..
햄 냄새는 맡을수 있겠네요
but at least it's gonna smell like ham
in here.
우리 애들은 지금
놀이방에 있어요
My kid's in a play right now.
여러분이 기운날 만한
소식을 전해주죠
You know what?
I know what will cheer you up.
본사에 얘기를 했어요
여러분의 노고에 대해 얘기했더니
I had a talk with the boys in New York.
I told them about all your hard work..
작은 보너스를 주더군요
and that a little Christmas bonus
may be in order.
"귀하의 이름으로 뉴욕 시립발레단에
기부했습니다"?
"A donation has been made in your name
to the New York City Ballet."
그게 그거죠, 뭐
Well, that's like money in your pocket.
좋아요! 인정합니다!
All right, you want me to say it?
This sucks.
이건 말도 안돼요! 크리스마스에
일하는건 말도 안됩니다!
Being here sucks. This work sucks!
이제 좀 크리스마스 기분이 나네요
Now it feels like Christmas.
미안해요
I'm sorry.
그래도 여러분은 저녁에
집에 가서 가족들을 볼수있죠
At least you get to go home
and be with your families tonight.
난 텅빈 호텔방에 가서
I have to go to an empty hotel room
and lay down..
찜찜하기 짝이 없는
침대에 누워야 해요
on a very questionable bedspread.
내일 아침 여러분은 집에서
크리스마스를 맞겠죠
Then tomorrow, you get to have
Christmas in your own houses.
그건 그렇고 아무도
날 초대하지 않더군요
Which, by the way,
none of you have invited me to.
- 우리집에 오세요!
- 아니, 됐어요
- You can come to my house.
- No, thanks.
- 멋진 격려연설이었어요
- 고마워요
- It was a nice pep talk.
- Thanks.
사실 전문적인 연설가로 나갈까
생각중이에요
I'm actually thinking about becoming
a motivational speaker.
지금 집에 있다면
보통 뭘 하시죠?
So if you were home right now,
what would you be doing?
뭔가 크리스마스다운 일을 하겠죠
Typical Christmassy stuff, you know.
Our holidays are pretty traditional.
전통적인 방식으로
지내는 편이니까
소중한 사람들을 위해 작곡한
So here's a very special
holiday song..
특별한 크리스마스 노래입니다
that I wrote for some
very important people to me.
백화점 산타 무릎에 앉아
친구들에게 선물 달라 졸랐지
친구들 위해 노래만
지으면 된다 하셨네
처음듣는 노래일 테니
절대 따라 부르지마
따라 부르지마
모니카, 모니카
해피 하누카
산타 클로스
로스에게 인사하네
조이에게 말해주오
크리스마스에 눈 내린다고!
레이첼과 챈들러에겐..
즐거운 명절 되세요!
Happy holidays, everybody.
피비, 넌 부엌 뒤져!
난 옷장속을 볼께!
Phoebe, look in the kitchen.
I'll look in the back closet.
그럴거 없어
나 여기 있다구!
I can save you time, ladies.
I'm right here.
넌 산책이나 하고와
Yeah. Chandler,
why don't you take a walk.
너랑은 상관없는 일이니까
This doesn't concern you.
모니카가 우릴위해 준비한
크리스마스 선물을 찾아야해
We are looking for
our Christmas presents from Monica.
- 뭐? 그런법이 어디 있어!
- 매년 해온 거니까 괜찮아
- What? That's terrible.
- No, no. We do it every year.
매년하면 그래도 되는거래?
Well, that makes it not terrible.
한번도 성공한 적이 없어!
항상 우리를 따돌렸다구
No. Yeah, we never find them.
She's always bested us, that wily..
고 앙큼한 계집애가!
minx.
걱정마
여기 1시간만 뒤지고
We're gonna search here
for an hour..
조이네 집 뒤질거야, 됐지?
and then we'll go to Joey's
and search. Okay?
안돼!
모니카 선물 뒤지지마!
No, not okay.
You can't look for Monica's presents.
- 그래야해!
- 안돼!
- No, we have to.
- No, you don't have to.
허락할수 없어!
여긴 내 집이기도 해!
And you can't,
because I live here too.
- 그럼 너도 같이 찾아보자
- 왜?
- Well, then you should look with us.
- Why?
넌 모니카한테 무슨 선물
해야할지 걱정도 안돼?
Aren't you worried about what
to get Monica for Christmas?
아니, 멋진 선물 하나
생각해뒀는걸
No, I have a great idea
for a present for her.
그것뿐이야?
"멋진 선물 하나"?
That's it? "A great idea"?
그정도로는 부족해
모니카는 멋진것 한개
That's not enough.
What if she gets you a great present..
보통 두개에
작은 선물 무더기를 줄텐데
two medium presents
and lots of little presents..
넌 달랑 하나 준다구?
모니카가 서운해 할걸?
and you got her one great present?
That's gonna make her feel bad.
모니카한테 그러고 싶어?
대체 왜? 왜그러는 건데?
Why would you do that to her?
Why? Why?
- 내가 도와주면 빨리 찾겠지?
- 물론이야!
- If I helped, we could find them faster!
- Right.
- 여기 포장 안한게 있어!
- 백화점 가방이네!
- We have a live one!
- It's a Macy's bag!
누구 선물일까?
Who's it for?
"가엾은 중생들아, 내가 소파
밑에 숨길 사람으로 보이니?"
"Dear Losers: Do you really think
I'd hide presents under the couch?
"추신: 챈들러, 여자애들한테
넘어갈줄 알았어!"
P.S. Chandler,
I knew they'd break you."
레이첼, 이거 네 선물이야
Rach, these are for you.
자동차 와이퍼네!
난 차도 없는데
Wiper blades. I don't even have a car.
하지만 이 새차 냄새
방향제면 기분이 날거야!
No, but with this new-car smell,
you'll think you do.
피비, 이건 네거
Okay, Phoebe, your turn.
와! 변기 커버네!
Toilet seat covers!
아까 차에 기름 넣는동안
이거 준비 한거야?
Is that what you were doing
while I was getting gas?
기특하기도 해라!
You guys.
그리고 로스
이건 네거
And for Ross, Mr. Sweet Tooth.
- 콜라 잖아?
- 게다가 레몬 쥬스도 있어!
- You got me a cola drink?
- And.. a lemon-lime!
와, 너무 큰 선물이라
Well, this.. This is too much.
너희들 스웨터 하나씩
더 사줘야겠다
I feel like I should get you
another sweater.
마지막으로..
And last but not least..
너의 쾌감을 위해
특별한 모양으로 골랐어
They're ribbed, for your pleasure.
벤?
Well, hey, Ben?
크리스마스 아마딜로가
불빛 축제에 대해 얘기해줄까?
What if the Holiday Armadillo
told you all about the Festival of Lights?
- 좋아요!
- 그래!
Cool!
이리와, 벤
Come on, Ben.
아주 오랜 옛날 맥카비라는
성을 가진 사람들이 살았단다
Years and years ago, there were
these people called the Maccabees!
호 호 호! 메리 크리스마스!
Merry Christmas!
산타할아버지!
Santa!
여긴 웬일이에요, 산타?
What are you doing here, Santa?
내 친구 벤을 만나러 왔지
Well, I'm here to see my old buddy Ben.
당신은 여기 웬일이죠?
What are you doing here..
괴상한.. 거북이 아저씨?
weird turtle-man?
난 크리스마스 아마딜로예요!
산타의 유태인 친구말예요!
I'm the Holiday Armadillo,
your part-Jewish friend.
산타가 벤에게 선물
You sent me here to give Ben
some presents.
갖다주라고 했잖아요
Remember?
뭐라구?
What?
벤, 선물 풀어봐
Ben, why don't you open
some more presents.
고모는 산타랑 아마딜로랑
얘기좀 할게
Santa, the armadillo and I
will have a talk in the kitchen.
이런 말하게 될줄은
꿈에도 몰랐네
There's a sentence I never thought
I'd say.
어떻게 된거야?
What are you doing?
네가 산타옷 못 구했다길래
You called and said you had trouble
finding a Santa costume..
직장 동료한테 빌렸지
so I borrowed one
from a guy at work.
고맙긴 하지만
그냥 가주면 좋겠다
Thank you, but you gotta leave.
- 왜?
- 벤이
- Why?
- Because..
겨우 하누카에 대해
관심을 갖기 시작했어
I'm finally getting him excited
about Hanukkah.
산타가 있으면
물거품이 될거야
And you're wrecking it.
아직 젤리처럼 출렁출렁한 배도
흔들어보지 못했는걸
But I didn't get to shake my belly
like a bowl full of jelly.
미안하지만 나에겐
아주 중요한 일이야
I'm sorry, Chandler,
but this is really important to me.
알았어
옷 돌려줄게
Okay, fine. I'll give the suit back.
하룻밤 더 빌릴수 있어?
Hey, you think you can keep it
another night?
산타랑? 진심이야?
Santa? Really?
- 그래, 빌릴수 있어?
- 아빠가 산타로 변장하신적 없어?
- Yeah, is that okay?
- Did your dad ever dress up like Santa?
- 없어
- 그럼 대찬성이야!
- No.
- Then it's okay!
여러분!
You know what, everybody?
퇴근해요!
가족들한테로 가세요
Go home.
You should be with your families.
31일도 일해야 하잖아요
It's bad enough we're working
New Year's Eve.
31일 근무하는 것에 대해
아무한테도 말 안했던가요?
Did I not tell anyone
about New Year's Eve?
다들 가보세요
메리 크리스마스!
All right, look, go. Go home, okay?
Merry Christmas.
- 메리 크리스마스
- 메리 크리스마스!
- Merry Christmas.
- Peace on earth.
- 잘보내요, 갈게요
- 메리 크리스마스, 조심해서 가요!
- Bye.
- Good. Godspeed, good people.
- 안가요?
- 혼자두고 갈순 없잖아요
- You're not gonna go?
- No. I couldn't leave you alone.
고마워요
Thanks.
게다가 아래층 파티 끝나기 전엔
나갈수 없어요
Besides, I can't leave until that
Christmas party downstairs clears out.
몇사람이 화가 잔뜩나서
그 햄 찾고 있거든요
There are some pissed-off
insurance people looking for that ham.
- 챈들러 빙입니다
- 우리 여기 다 모였어
- Chandler Bing.
- Hi, honey. We're all here.
크리스마스 인사하려구
We want to wish you
a merry Christmas.
- 메리 크리스마스!
- Merry Christmas!
메리 크리스마스!
모두들 보고싶다
Merry Christmas. I miss you guys.
힘들지?
다들 열심히 일하는 거야?
So is it horrible?
Is everybody working really hard?
아냐, 나랑 웬디 뿐이야
Well, no, it's just me and Wendy.
웬디? 여자이름 같네?
Wendy? That sounds like a girl's name.
맞아, 내가 얘기 안했나?
It is. Did I not tell you about her?
31일도 근무해야한다는
얘기 할때쯤 했던가?
About the time you told me
about New Year's Eve.
- 다른 사람들은?
- 집으로 가라고 했어
- Where's everybody else?
- I sent them home.
자긴 참 좋은 상사야
그 여자 예뻐?
You are such a good boss.
Is she pretty?
빨리 대답해, 빨리!
Answer faster. Answer faster.
- 글쎄
- 잘 대답해, 잘!
- I don't know.
- Answer better. Answer better.
그런쪽으론 생각 안해봤거든
직장 동료니까
I don't think of her that way.
I mean, she's a colleague.
- 그 여잔 무슨일 하는데?
- 부지점장이야
- What does she do there?
- She's regional vice president.
- 내 바로 밑에 있어
- 뭐가 어째?!
- She's just below me.
- She did what?
내 밑에 있다구!
Below me.
웬디라면 미스 오클라호마
2등 했다는 여자 아냐?
Wait, is Wendy the runner-up
Miss Oklahoma?
뭐야?
What?!
1등은 못했어
Well, she didn't win.
그럼 오클라호마에서
All right, maybe I should let you..
두번째로 예쁜 여자랑
일 잘해봐
and the second prettiest girl
in Oklahoma get back to work.
그해 두번째로 예뻤던 거야
그러니까, 오클라호마 여자들 중에서..
Second prettiest that year. Of all
the girls in Oklahoma, she's probably..
챈들러! 입 다물어!
Chandler, stop talking.
아무것도 걱정할것 없어
Honey, there's really
nothing to worry about.
- 알았어
- 정말이야
- Okay.
- I'm serious.
그래
Okay.
- 메리 크리스마스
- Merry Christmas.
- 모두들 메리 크리스마스!
- 메리 크리스마스!
- Merry Christmas, you guys.
- Merry Christmas.
- 집사람 전화예요
- 통화 재미있었어요?
- The wife says hi.
- Fun conversation?
웬디와 단둘이 있다니까
Well, she's just got
this weird idea that..
무슨일 생길까봐
괜한 걱정을 하네요
because you and I are alone
something's gonna happen.
정말요?
Really?
무슨일 있으면 큰일나나요?
Would that be so terrible?
난 걱정할 일
아니라고 생각하지만..
This is probably the wrong thing
to be worrying about..
하나뿐인 넥타이에
햄을 묻히면 어떡해요
but you're getting ham
on my only tie.
- 어! 물러서요, 아가씨!
- 아가씨?
- Back off, missy!
- Missy?
여자가 다가오는거
익숙치가 않아서요
I don't know. I'm not used to girls
making passes at me.
잠깐, 오클라호마에선
내가 매력적인가요?
Wait a minute.
Am I sexy in Oklahoma?
- 내눈에는 그래요
- 아녜요, 설마.. 안돼요!
- You are to me.
- No. No. No!
- 난 결혼했어요
- 나도 했어요
- Look, I'm married.
- So? I'm married.
결혼생활도 행복해요
I'm happily married.
어떤게 행복한 건데요?
What's that like?
- 미안하지만..
- 진심이에요? 행복한 결혼생활?
- Right. So I'm sorry, but..
- Seriously? Happily married?
그럼 아까 그 전화통화도
행복했나요?
So that phone call before,
that was happy?
부부가 이렇게 오랜 시간
떨어져 있는건 힘든 일이에요
Well, look, it's not easy
to spend this much time apart.
집사람이 좀 과민해도
무리가 아니죠
She's entitled to be
a little paranoid.
이번 경우엔
과민한 것도 아니지만
Or, in this case, right on the money.
아내는 굉장한 여자예요
아름답고 똑똑하고..
You know, she's amazing
and beautiful and smart.
지금 여기 있었으면
웬디 엉덩이 걷어찼을걸요
And if she were here right now,
she'd kick your ass.
웬디는 좋은 사람이에요
햄 도둑질과 바람기는 제쳐두고 말이죠
Look, you're a really nice person,
ham-stealing and adultery aside.
하지만 지금 아내와 난
아주 좋아요
But what I have with my wife
is pretty great.
그러니까 웬디와는
아무일 없을 거예요
So nothing's ever gonna happen
between us.
하나만 물어 볼게요
Okay, let me ask you something.
아내와 그렇게 사이가 좋다면
If what you and your wife have
is so great..
왜 크리스마스에 나와 함께 있죠?
then why are you spending
Christmas with me?
오늘 피로연 장에서
네가 제일 아름다웠어
You were the most beautiful woman
in the room tonight.
- 정말?
- 물론이지!
- Really?
- Are you kidding?
넌 어디에 가도
제일 아름다울거야
You're the most beautiful woman
in most rooms.
어! 방금 이게 뭐지?
우리 방금 키스했어!
What's going on?
You and I just made out.
- 우리 키스한 거야?
- 지금은 아니지
- You and I are making out?
- Well, not anymore.
- 우리 그러면 안되잖아!
- 알지만, 재미있을것 같았어
- But we don't do that.
- I know. I just thought it would be fun.
- 얼마나 취했어?
- 이러고 싶다는거 알만큼은 취했어
- How drunk are you?
- Drunk enough that I wanna do this.
네가 술취한 애 이용했다고
죄책감 느낄 만큼은 아니구
Not so drunk that you should
feel guilty about taking advantage.
딱 적당히 취했네
That's a perfect amount.
- 이상하지 않아?
- 뭐가?
- You know what's weird?
- What?
- 이러는거 하나도 안이상해!
- 그러게!
- This doesn't feel weird.
- I know.
- 키스 잘하는데?
- 지금까지 여자 네명이랑 해봤어
- You're a really good kisser.
- Well, I have kissed over four women.
- 이불속으로 들어갈까?
- 그래
You wanna get under the covers?
Okay.
와! 진짜 빠르다!
Wow, you are really fast.
내 속도에 반했다니
예감이 좋은걸?
It bodes well for me
that speed impresses you.
- 서로 알몸 보게 되겠네?
- 그렇지
- We're gonna see each other naked.
- Yep.
- 우리 동시에 볼까?
- 셋하면 보는거다
- You want to do it at the same time?
- Count of three?
- 하나.. 둘
- 둘
- One.
- Two.
- 셋!
Three.
우리의 우정은 완벽하게
박살났다고 볼수 있겠군
Well, I think it's safe to say
that our friendship is effectively ruined.
- 별로 친하지도 않았잖아
- 맞아
We weren't that close anyway.
정말 저 남자간호사랑
데이트 할거야?
Are you really gonna go out
with that nurse-man?
우리가 그냥 재미보는 사이라면
Well, you and I
are just goofing around.
그 남자랑 재미 못볼것도 없잖아
I thought, why not
just goof around with him?
"재미본다"라는 말을 사전에서
찾아봤는지 모르겠는데
I don't know if you've ever looked up
"goofing around" in the dictionary.
난 찾아봤거든
Well, I have.
그 정확한 뜻은 말야
And the technical definition
is two friends..
서로 몹시 아끼며
근사한 잠자리까지 나누고
who care a lot about each other
and have amazing sex..
함께 더 많은 시간을 보내고 싶은
친구들 사이에 쓰는 말이야
and just want to spend
more time together.
자기가 신식 사전 때문에
나한테 화가 난것 같은데
If you have this newfangled dictionary
that gets you mad at me..
그렇다면 내 원판사전
빌려줄게
then we have to, you know,
get you my original dictionary.
나 정말 어설프지?
I am so bad at this.
자기가 생각하는 것보다는
훨씬 괜찮아
I think you're better
than you think you are.
- 정말? 좋아, 그럼 만약..
- 더하면 주책이야
- Really? Okay. So if..?
- Know when to stop.
안그래도 여기서 그만해야
한다고 생각했어
I sensed that I should stop.
- 그럼 우리 괜찮은거지?
- 그래
- So we're okay?
- Yeah.
- 춤추지마!
- 알았어
- Don't do the dance.
- Right.
낡은것, 새것, 빌린것
I can't get married without
something old, something new..
- 파란것 없으면 결혼 못해!
- 알았어
- something borrowed, something blue.
- Okay, okay.
이거 파란 색에 새거야!
Here's something blue and new.
똑똑하기도 하지!
사랑해!
You are so efficient. I love you.
- 가자
- 잠깐!
- Let's go.
- No, no, wait!
낡은것도 있어야해
We need something old.
지갑속에 12살 때부터
갖고 다닌 콘돔이 있어
Okay. I have a condom in my wallet
that I've had since I was 12.
그거면 될거야!
That'll work!
성능은 의심스러워
I don't think so.
이제 남한테 빌린 물건만
있으면돼
Okay. Now we just need
something borrowed.
- 이거 가져가자
- 도둑질이잖아!
- Here, just take this.
- That's stealing.
다시 갖다 놓으면 되지
옷속에 숨겨
We'll bring it back.
Just put it under your dress.
한번에 하나씩만 하자
Okay, one thing at a time.
있잖아..
Listen..
생각해 봤는데
I've been thinking.
자기 돈 결혼식에 몽땅 쓰자고
한건 억지였어
It's not fair for me to ask you to spend
all of your money on our wedding.
자기가 "정말 열심히"
일해서 번거잖아
I mean, you work..
You work really hard for that.
- 글쎄, 뭐..
- 아무튼 일해서 번거잖아
- Well..
- Well, you work for that.
나도 생각해 봤어
Look, I've thought about it too. And..
미안해, 그돈 우리 결혼식에
전부 쓰자
I'm sorry. I think we should spend
all of the money on the wedding.
- 정말?
- 그래, 내 결심 확고해
- You do?
- Yeah. I'm putting my foot down.
청혼할때
Yeah, look, when I proposed..
널 행복하게 하는 일이라면
뭐든지 하겠다고 했어
I told you that I would do anything
to make you happy.
완벽한 결혼식으로
네가 행복할수 있다면..
And if having the perfect wedding
makes you happy, then..
그렇게 하는거야
Then that's what we're gonna do.
정말 고마워
You are so sweet.
그렇지만 우리 미래는
어떡하구?
But wait. What about our..?
What about the future and stuff?
미래 따위는 잊어버리자
애도 둘만 낳아서
Forget about the future and stuff.
So we only have two kids.
맘에 드는 애 하나만
대학에 보내자구
You know, we'll pick our favorite,
and that one will get to go to college.
- 그런 생각도 했어?
- 그럼
- You've thought about that?
- Yeah.
- 원래는 아이 몇명 생각했는데?
- 네명, 아들 하나, 쌍둥이 딸
- How many kids were we gonna have?
- Four. A boy, twin girls..
그리고 또 아들
and another boy.
- 또 무슨 생각했어?
- 그리고..
- What else did you think about?
- Well..
어디서 살면 좋을까
뭐 그런거지
stuff like where we'd live, you know.
시 외곽에 애들이 자전거 타고
놀수있는 아담한 집에서 사는거야
Like a small place outside the city
where our kids could ride bikes and stuff.
방울 단 고양이도 키우자
And we could have a cat
that had a bell on its collar..
움직일 때마다
방울소리가 날거야
and we could hear it every time
it ran through the little kitty door.
우리 조이가 여생을 보낼수 있게
차고 위에 방도 만들고
We'd have an apartment over the garage
where Joey could grow old.
나 말야
You know what?
성대한 결혼식 필요없어
I don't..
I don't want a big, fancy wedding.
- 아냐, 그렇게해
- 정말이야
- Sure you do.
- No.
방금 자기가 말한게 더 좋아
I want everything
that you've just said.
결혼식말고 결혼생활
I want a marriage.
- 정말이야?
- 그래
You sure?
- 사랑해
- I love you so much.
- I love you.
- 와! 예쁘다!
- 정말? 안바꿀 거야?
- I love it!
- Really? You're not gonna return it?
지금 당장은 아냐!
Well, not this second.
얘들아, 눈온다!
Hey, look, you guys. It's snowing!
- 와, 참 예쁘다!
- 정말 멋있다
- Wow, it's so beautiful.
- Wow, it really is.
웬디라는 여자
뚱뚱할것 같아
Wendy's a fat-girl name.
아직도 그 생각이야?
Aren't we done with that?
알았어, 눈 얘기 하자구
Okay, fine. Fine.
Let's talk about snow.
내 남편이 사무실에서 여자랑
뒹굴고 있는 털사에도 눈이 올까?
Do you think it's snowing in Tulsa where
my husband's having sex on a copier?
- 얘들아!
- 어라?
- Hey.
- Oh, my God.
야! 크리스마스의 기적이야!
Look at that.
That's a Christmas miracle!
- 어떻게 된거야?
- 자기랑 있고 싶어서
- What are you doing here?
- I wanted to be with you.
너희들 너무 보고 싶었어
I missed you so much.
- 누가 제일 보고 싶었는데?
- 모니카
- Hey, hey. Who'd you miss the most?
- Monica.
알았어
Gotcha.
- 다시는 안떠날게
- 일 못하면 잘린다며?
- I never want to leave you again.
- I thought if you left, you'd get fired.
회사에선 이제 나 못잘라
내가 그만뒀거든
Turns out they can't fire me.
Because I quit.
- 뭐?
- 정말 사표 냈어?
- What?
- What? You..? You really quit your job?
한심한 일이었어
자기랑 떨어져있는 것도 싫고
Yeah. It was a stupid job,
and I could not stand leaving you.
정말 하고싶은 일 못하는
유일한 사람인 것도 싫어!
Why should I be the only one who
doesn't do what he really wants to do?
- 정말 하고 싶은 일이 뭔데?
- 아직 거기까지는 생각 안해봤어
- Well, what do you really wanna do?
- I have not thought this through.
- 세상에!
- 자기랑 먼저 상의해야 했는데 미안해
- Oh, my God.
- I know. I should've talked to you first.
아냐, 자기가 원하는 거라면
잘한거야!
No, I think that this is what
you wanna do. I think it's great!
고마워
Thanks.
챈들러, 네가 돌아온건 나에겐
최고의 크리스마스 선물이야
Chandler, your being here is the best
Christmas present I could ever imagine.
- 이제 진짜 선물줘
- 알았어
- Now give me my real gift.
- Yeah.
- 고마워
- 하나씩 가져
- Thank you.
- Here, pass those around.
"귀하의 이름으로 뉴욕 시립발레단에
기부했습니다"?
"A donation has been made in your name
to the New York City Ballet."
내가 기부한거 어떻게 알았어?
How did you know?
장난하니?
이건 바꾸지도 못하잖아!
What? Are you kidding?
I can't return this.
이웃에 대해 생각해야 할때라고
생각하지 않니?
It's time we started thinking about
other people.
그리고 그 선물에도 너희에 대한
내 사랑이 담겨있다구
And besides, this gift still says,
"I love you guys."
- '릴리안 마이어스 귀하'라고 써있는데!
- 나 실직자란 말야!
- Mine says, "To Lillian Myers."
- I don't have a job.
보험설계사? 싫어
Actuary? No.
회계사? 싫어
Bookkeeper? No.
술집 댄서?
Topless dancer?
방금 뭘 깨달았는지 알아?
자기는 이제 이 집안의 생계를
Hey, you know what I just realized?
You are the sole wage earner.
책임지고 있는 가장이야! 난 아무것도
안해도 돼! 난 기둥서방이다!
You are the head of the household.
I don't do anything. I'm a kept man!
맞아
You are.
20달러야
Honey, here's 20 bucks.
나 내일 일하는 동안
예쁜옷 사 입어
Go buy yourself something pretty
while I'm at work tomorrow.